Where am I?
My... mother?
No, it can't be.
My mom is much more...
I can barely move.
What's going on?
Name: None
Sex: Male
Level: 1
/
∞
HP: F
Fire: F
MP: F
Water: E
Strength: F
Wind: F
Stamina: F
Earth: F
Intelligence: F
Light: F
Spirit: F
Dark: F
Speed: F
Dexterity: F
Are those... my stats?
My level's gone back to 1.
And... no name?
Your Majesty.
No need. As you were.
"Your Majesty"?!
What a fine face he has.
His brow resembles yours.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I believe his mouth looks just like yours.
Is this old man an emperor or something?
What in the world... is happening... to me?
What shall his name be?
Noah. Noah Ararat.
He shall hold the title of
Thirteenth Imperial Prince.
Thank you.
Name: Thirteenth Imperial Prince Noah Ararat
Sex: Male
Level: 1
/
∞
Imperial prince?
That's a title given only to the son
of an emperor, a noble among nobles!
What is Noah's affinity?
Water, Your Majesty.
Then his fief shall be Almeria, a land
where many of the Water Clan reside.
Fire
Water
Wind
Yes, sire.
Plus?!
What is this? I've never
seen values like these!
That's one matter settled.
Cruz, show me his skills.
Yes, sire.
Pardon me, Your Highness.
By the power invested in me by the spirits,
show me this individual's true
purpose and disposition.
Name: Thirteenth Imperial Prince Noah Ararat
Sex: Male
Level: 1
/
∞
HP: F
Fire: F
MP: F
Water: SS
Strength: F
Wind: F
Stamina: F
Earth: F
Intelligence: F
Light: F
What's this?
Water
The value changed.
This can't be... It's so much
higher than when he was born...
Does this mean he has already awakened?
Splendid!
I've never heard of anyone
reaching SS at that age!
As expected of our emperor's child!
We are witnessing the birth
of a man of immense talent!
Whatever the case, I have
been granted a new life
and reincarnated as a noble.
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
Episode 1
Thirteenth Imperial Prince Noah Ararat
Meeres Empire is a nation of warriors
nestled in a craggy mountain range.
The capital is situated on an open plain.
As it enjoys its golden age in
which wealth begets wealth,
a rich, resplendent culture
now blooms in this nation.
Its emperor is the father to over ten
sons known as the Imperial Princes,
who are revered and adored by the people
as the most renowned of nobles.
Good morning, Prince Noah.
Six years after my reincarnation,
I've realized something.
Name: Thirteenth Imperial Prince Noah Ararat
Sex: Male
Level: 1
/
∞
HP: F
Fire: F
MP: F
Water: SS
Strength: F
Wind: F
Stamina: F+F
Earth: F
Intelligence: F
Light: F
Spirit: F
Dark: F
Speed: F
Dexterity: F+F
This is how my stats look to everyone else,
Water
Wind
but to me, they look like this.
These are additions made by my subordinates.
Noah Ararat
Age 6
Thirteenth Prince
The S added to Water, for example,
came from Almeria, the fief
I was granted at birth.
The others came from my maids.
In other words, I can grow stronger
by gaining more subordinates.
Name: Thirteenth Imperial Prince Noah Ararat
Sex: Male
Level: 1
/
∞
And my level...
can be raised infinitely, I suppose?
Thank you for your patience.
You look very handsome again today.
Good.
He is remarkable, isn't he?
Most boys his age would be full of mischief,
but he is so calm and composed.
Perhaps that is what they
call a "regal bearing."
That said, my capabilities are
quite limited at age six.
Pardon me.
Evelyn is a beautiful maid who
specializes in hospitality.
Evelyn
Beautiful
Specializes in Hospitality
The Crown Prince and the Fourth
Prince have come to visit.
They say you can take your time
eating before going to see them.
I most certainly cannot.
He's the Crown Prince.
Take me at once.
Good morning, dear brother.
Ah, there you are.
Albert Ararat
Age 29
Crown Prince, Second Prince
I had just finished my meal.
Sure, we'll leave it at that.
I see Noah is as courteous as ever.
Henry Ararat
Age 21
Fourth Prince
Yes. He'll be a fine chancellor one day.
I will do my best to achieve that.
We have a present for you today.
What is it?
Open it.
N-No! It's going to eat me!
Please! Please spare me!
Please save us, Prince Albert!
What was that?
What do you think?
Nice sword, isn't it?
Y-Yes...
Pick it up.
It's a gift from the Crown Prince.
I can't refuse.
Very well.
Oh? I should have known.
That sword is called Leviathan.
It is a water magic sword known
as the strongest in the empire.
Around 120 people have
died trying to master it.
That was close! I almost dropped
the Crown Prince's gift!
Worry not.
Those not meant to wield it are killed
by its curse the moment they lift it.
For most people, just carrying
the box is agonizing.
I see. So one with water affinity
at level SS can wield it.
This has been a valuable demonstration.
Sorry to interrupt your morning.
That despicable Crown Prince was testing me?
No. If I say that out loud, I'm dead.
Was that wise?
That sword must be priceless.
No matter.
It's better off in the hands of
someone as brilliant as him.
Besides...
it's precisely because he's so brilliant
that he needs to experience being
bitten by his own precious pet.
Zoey, is something wrong?
You seem unhappy.
F-Forgive me. You needn't worry.
It's all right. Speak.
Then, when you have time later—
Zoey.
The truth is... I'd like
to request some time off.
Zoey
Age 18
Noah's Personal Maid
Has something happened?
There was a flood in my hometown recently.
The farm where I grew up was washed out,
and my mother, who lives
alone, is now out of work.
And... my relatives have told me to
work in the red-light district.
They say even I could sell myself
as someone who served a prince—
I've heard enough.
Very well. I will employ your
mother here at the mansion.
Let's see...
I will put her in charge
of locking the rear gate.
I'll pay her ten rean per month.
What? B-But, Master,
I've never heard of such a job!
And that is far higher
than the standard wage...
There's an unused house in the
western outskirts of the capital.
You and your mother can use it.
Thank you!
Continue your work.
Of course!
A former servant of mine
working in the red-light district?
If I allow that, I'll sully the
title of Thirteenth Prince.
She's my servant,
so she will serve me for life.
Dylan.
I am here.
There's been a flood in
Zoey's hometown, Dosso.
Are you aware of it?
Yes.
Buy as much of the land there as possible.
What?
There will be villains trying to con
people who've lost their livelihoods,
like Zoey's family, out of their fortunes.
Secure them before that happens.
What is it?
Oh, I am merely surprised to see you
handling a situation you've never
experienced before with such foresight.
I saw more than my share of
it before I reincarnated.
But I can't tell him that.
But how shall I procure the funds?
By my estimate, that would require
approximately 700,000 rean.
Seven hun—
Forgive me.
I can't blame her for being surprised.
The average annual income of an adult
man in the capital is 120 rean.
Even my own retainers earn
eight thousand rean per year.
Emperor
Thirteenth Prince
Almeria
Add in the tax revenue from Almeria
and monetary gifts from the emperor,
and the Thirteenth Prince's household
has about 500,000 rean to work with.
500,000R
That leaves 200,000.
We own land south of the capital, yes?
We'll have to sell it.
Wha—But that land was
a gift from His Majesty!
To sell it without his permission would
be a crime against the imperial family!
That's fine. I will accept
my father's reproach.
But...
Prince Noah!
Nobles have their obligations.
Sometimes, they must sacrifice themselves
to bring happiness to as many
of their people as possible.
Playing the martyr is one of the
privileges of the nobility.
Yes, Your Highness. As you wish.
Also, Prince Noah...
What is it?
Dylan
The Thirteenth Prince's Butler
Thank you very much.
That's right.
I forgot Dylan also came
from that same area.
This goes inside.
Oh, wait. Yes, put that one in
the second carriage, please.
And all of those can go
in the first carriage.
Awfully busy out here.
I'm sorry! I failed to come and greet you,
Brother Henry.
Think nothing of it.
Anyway, are you going somewhere?
Yes. I'm purchasing land in an area
called Dosso, which has flooded.
I'm going to inspect it.
Oh? Well that's...
Brother?
Do you intend to use the magic sword?
No, I did sense some sort of power in
it, but I haven't felt it since then.
I'm just taking it with me as a test.
I see.
Is that why you came to talk to me alone?
Since Albert said such strange
things, I looked into it.
It seems that sword has a will of its own.
A will?
Apparently, it only obeys the one
it recognizes as its master.
I must earn its recognition.
Please! Please spare me!
It's like a mad dog.
Carry it with you if you
must, but don't use it.
You will die.
How awful...
Dylan, go to the government office.
By which you mean...
From the looks of it, I'd say most of the
ruined homes lost their land deeds, as well.
We'll have to purchase them based
on the government office's lists.
I-I see...
I'm amazed you ascertained
that from just one look.
If anything happens, I'll
assume responsibility. Hurry.
It will be done, Your Highness.
Zoey, come with me. I need
to know the lay of the land.
O-Of course!
So the root vegetables have
already started to rot?
There'll be no harvest this year.
I still think this is dangerous, Master.
You didn't need to come this far.
If you insist on stopping me,
I'll sneak out alone overnight.
But... I can't let you...
They're distributing food.
Looks like the empire is doing its job.
It's so bland. It's barely
more than boiled water.
Are you all right?
This tastes horrible!
Is it already spoiled?
This can't be—
We can't ask for too much.
We're just lucky we get
to eat, even if it's this.
We must accept it gratefully.
But I can't believe the empire
would distribute food like this...
Oh, boy. Here he comes.
Inspection!
Who's that?
The local government official, Lord Garil.
Here it is.
Hmm... Looks all right.
Thank you, sir.
Your portion is ready in the mansion.
Thorough as always, I see.
Getting kickbacks for this?
H-Hey!
Master!
Who are you, boy?
Did you hire them for kickbacks?
Huh?
You did, didn't you?
Big talk for such a little boy!
This is tough work for us, too, you know.
Taking a little something in return
is a privilege afforded to
those of us who give so much!
Exactly!
You just learned a valuable lesson, boy!
To call me a child is condescending.
Getting rich off of rations intended
for disaster victims is a crime.
What was that, you rotten little brat?
To insult me is to insult
Sir Rowen, the ruler of this land!
Do you realize—
Tyrannizing the weak to curry
favor with the strong...
Would you like to hear your sentence?
Enough of your nonsense!
Reminds me of that sword...
You rotten little brat!
It's death!
Master!
I bet you're angry that I associated
you with the likes of this trash, huh?
If so, then show me your strength.
So you are the strong one...
and I am the weak one, then?
That's very small of you!
The strong only flaunt their
power before the weak
because they fear someone even stronger!
If you were born strong...
If you succeeded in being born strong...
then use that power for
the good of the people!
That is my privilege as a noble!
Obey me, Leviathan!
Die!
Lord Garil!
You brat!
Apprehend that child!
Wait!
I-Incredible...
I can't even see the bottom.
You are insane, you know that?
Wh-What's going on?!
Let us through!
What the...
Please save us!
Lord Garil... Lord Garil was
murdered by that child!
A child?
Rowen
Knight Captain Who Rules Dosso
I-I apologize for being unaware that
you were visiting, Thirteenth Prince!
Sir Rowen?!
You know who I am?
Yes. I am Rowen Green.
I was only recently appointed to maintain
security in this region.
I am a servant of Prince Henry's house.
Oh, my brother?
What's going on?
Sir Rowen is...
What are you people doing?!
Who is that child?
You are in the presence of
His Highness the Thirteenth Prince!
What's the meaning of this?
Rowen, I'll be borrowing you for a bit.
Of course. I am at your service.
Someone hired these food
distributors for kickbacks.
I punished this man, who was behind it all.
Those men are his accomplices.
Deal the punishment they deserve.
We'll start over with the food distribution.
Add more to that soup.
So much that I can stand a
spoon in it and it won't fall.
Can you do that?
Yes, Your Highness!
If it costs me my life!
We'll get to eat... proper food?
Long live the Thirteenth Prince!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Prince Noah, you are incredible.
Understood. Now go.
Not only did he not get bitten, but that
mad dog actually submitted to him?
He may be even more useful than I thought.
I am Noah Ararat.
I have come in answer to
His Majesty's summons.
I heard the reports.
You sold the land I granted you
and bought an entire village?
Here it comes...
I thank you.
Your efforts have prevented the emergence of
anyone trying to take advantage of the flood.
Were this natural disaster
followed by a man-made disaster,
we would have had to commit imperial
resources to cleaning up the mess.
Emperor of Meeres Empire
How did you learn of this?
It was coincidental.
One of my maids happens
to be from that village.
I see. Still, providence also played a part.
You mastered a water magic sword
in that village, did you not?
You knew about that?
It has been some time. I would like
to see Noah's abilities again.
Pardon me, Your Highness.
I guess it's not just human subordinates
that can add to my stats.
HP: F
Fire: F
MP: F
Water: E+SS
Strength: F+F
Wind: F
Stamina: F+F
Earth: F
This isn't what I usually see.
Splendid!
What the...
Name: Thirteenth Imperial Prince Noah Ararat
Sex: Male
Level: 1
/
∞
HP: F
Fire: F
MP: F
Water: SSS
Wind: F
Earth: F
Light: F
Dark: F
Water is now SSS, with no plus sign.
Noah.
I ask that you continue to
aid me with your talents.
Of course!